{
    "subject": "resource/David_Murray_(saxophonist)",
    "predicate": "ontology/hometown",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "David Murray (saxophonist) was born in the United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8309124708175659,
            "question": "Where was David Murray born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.454738587141037,
            "question": "What instrument is David Murray known for playing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4356038570404053,
            "question": "Where has David Murray performed throughout his career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3457213044166565,
            "question": "What genre of music is David Murray associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.30438584089279175,
            "question": "Has David Murray collaborated with other notable musicians?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.30029016733169556,
            "question": "Is David Murray considered a prominent figure in jazz music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2913461923599243,
            "question": "What impact has David Murray had on the music industry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.26917368173599243,
            "question": "Does David Murray compose his own music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1655884087085724,
            "question": "Has David Murray received any awards or recognition for his work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.11817380040884018,
            "question": "What are some of David Murray's most popular albums?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=David Murray (saxophonist) was born in the United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9047_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has David Murray received any awards or recognition for his work?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9047_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does David Murray compose his own music?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9047_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What impact has David Murray had on the music industry?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9047_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9047_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9047_113.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9047_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9047_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9047_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9047_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9047_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9047_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9047_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9047_90.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about David Murray's birthplace, stating that he was born in Oakland, California. Since California is part of the United States, the statement \"David Murray (saxophonist) was born in the United States\" is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}